<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hi, I&#39;m Anthony</title>
    <link>https://manschula.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hi, I&#39;m Anthony</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 10:27:58 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://manschula.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CPRE 381: VHDL Processor Design</title>
      <link>https://manschula.dev/projects/cpre381/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 10:33:47 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://manschula.dev/projects/cpre381/</guid>
      <description>CPRE 381: Computer Organization and Assembly Level Programming. This project as a whole spanned several months, from February until the end of the semester, with the overall goal of designing several processors around the MIPS ISA with the final goal of comparing their performance. It relied heavily on applying concepts from class, including VHDL skills, piplining, hazard avoidance, and general knowledge of digital logic and the MIPS ISA. All designs included in the below repository implement the core MIPS ISA, and will run an arbitrary MIPS assembly program (examples included).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyclone Racing CR-26</title>
      <link>https://manschula.dev/projects/cr26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 11:20:56 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://manschula.dev/projects/cr26/</guid>
      <description>Cyclone Racing Formula SAE Team. As mentioned in the above section, I am a member of ISU&amp;rsquo;s FSAE team, and I have been involved with the Powertrain subsystem since August 2021. CR-26 is the car that we designed and built for the 2021-2022 school year, and although I was still a new member at the time, I contributed to several key areas within the Powertrain subsystem, including designing an updated wiring diagram for the car, and assisting with wiring and engine calibration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CPRE 288: Embedded Systems I</title>
      <link>https://manschula.dev/projects/cpre288/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 10:33:47 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://manschula.dev/projects/cpre288/</guid>
      <description>CPRE 288: Embedded Systems I. The overall goal of this project was to develop code that would allow the group to navigate the vehicle (an iRobot Create 2) through a course entirely using onboard sensors, without the vehicle being directly visible to the group. As a whole, I learned a great deal about embedded systems and how they can be used to aggregate and process data from a variety of digital and analog sensors.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
